

# KABAGAMBAJULESVALENTIN

#### **PROFILE**

Date of Birth: 14th February 2000

Status: Single Gender: Male

Attributions: I am a student with robust problem-solving skills and a proven experience in creating good relations and adapting in a test-driven environment

# **SKILLS**

Languages Spoken.

French: proficient in both reading and

writing,

fluent in speaking and listening (DELF

certificate)

English: proficiency with DUOLINGO TEST. Fluent in writing, Reading and excellent in

speaking. Latin: basics

Kinyarwanda: My mother tongue

## CHARACTER REFERENCES

SHEMA KABERUKA VICTOR
Technical Team leader, ANDELA
Cell: +48 579 213 650

### **HOW TO REACH ME**

WhatsApp: +48 608 223 138

Cell: +48 608 223 138

Email: julesvalentin04@gmail.com

Address: Poland, POZNAN Połwiejska 9, 61-001 ZOOm ID: 944 695 8333

LinkedIn:

https://www.linkedin.com/in/jules-valentin-

kabagamba

## **CAREER SUMMARY**

HCL technologies
IT analyst

I DECLARE THAT THE INFORMATION

STATED ABOVE IS ALL TRUE.

2 Years experience, Interacted with users in GSK pharmaceuticals around the world but mostly french and english speakers, support them by troubleshooting, updating, installations with elevated accesses provided to me. Deal with Bug tracking, Ticketing with different operating systems and ticketing systems.

HR services in HCL Technologies
Dealing with Administration, management of performance and Using Active directory to troubleshoot user's issues and queries.

#### It informant

Garage Atecar | October 2020 to July 2021 Customer care to clients and their vehicles. Designs and maintain security software

solutions to solve against theft and mechanisms of cars of various clients.

Modifying updates of PCs and other monitors
Driving Skills
| March 2019 till Present
Developed, worked on car Mechanism
Evolved Driving skills
currently holding 2 categories and still want to increase them

#### **EDUCATIONAL TRAINING**

#### **WSKIZ UNIVERSITY POZNAN**

Enrolled since Sept. 2021 to present
Taking up specialization courses in ROBOTICS
AND AUTOMATIONS 3rd year, improving electives in
programming and technological mechanism of electrical

instruments mainly in the computer field.

ALX SOFTWARE ENGINEERING PROGRAMME

Pursued Software engineering since February 2022 to June 2022

PETIT SEMINAIRE VIRGO FIDELIS

Attended from Jan. 2014 to NOV 2019 Class representative and guild council

Instructor, Volleyball player either in National

team or Clubs and still going here in Poland in Tarnowo

Podgorne Ligua III Team.

Academic achievement awards

Bachelors of Science in Mathematics-Physics-Chemistry and Biology.

Advanced level certificate among the best candidates.